Hello friends, if you are all on your own
YouTube channel Is Me Investment,
friends, in today's video we are going to
talk about a stock which has been a
favorite of the investors and
even in a very weak market and in times like Covid, no
special collection was seen here
and currently this stock is
running on a multi gear lock,
we are talking about ICC Lombard General Insurance, the
stock of the company has performed very well, it is
quite broken from its high and the
near multi stock is trading, so
what strategy do you need in such a situation,
friends, if you want to do Is Me Investment, do
subscribe to our channel, we will tell you about all the
stocks listed in the insurance space,
maybe
you will make money in the stock, if I talk to you about some stock,
from IPS till now, maybe someone has made a lot of money,
India's largest company is
trading at a big discount,
Star Health is down the day before yesterday, apart from this, it has been
three, I will not say five years for life insurance companies,
ICC Life
is running below HDFC Life, SBI Life, but no big money has been
made in five-six years  While this
space is quite demanding, apart from this,
penetration in India is very low and the
long way to insurance is, if
you compare global India with the general
insurance business, then the demand is quite
huge. Just like the auto segment is
booming, so the demand here
is huge, but there is no big growth visible either in numbers or
in any particular stock. The
reason for this,
I will share with you further, this is the stock
of ICC Lombard, you will see that the stock is trading
around multi-year lows.
This stock is currently trading around the low it had made during the time of Covid. It has reached around
₹1200 after breaking its high of ₹1600.
Friends,
what is that reason, what is the thing that is pushing the
insurance sector apart, let's
talk about it in detail. Firstly, the claim
rates are very high, but in health
insurance plans in general insurance are
very high and due to competition, the
insurance companies are not
increasing the premium, which is the story, the story
margins.  is putting pressure, apart from this, the
competition has increased a lot here, if you
look at the insurance sector, then a lot of new age
digital companies have come,
I am not saying that they are taking away the
market share of the existing companies,
but the new business that is coming is
also going to them, this is a
very big region here, that
we are talking about, it has already come, another
factor friends, the factor of Reliance is also
very big, it is believed that
Reliance General Insurance can do a
big grand opening in the coming time,
hiring for that has already been done,
Financial Services, you will be
listed by October, it has a big
ambitious dream, that is in the General Insurance,
Health Insurance space, so the
market is trying to enter that sector too, although this is
not a confirmed news right now, but currently
also this sector has become very scattered
and a lot of companies have come,
three companies of this space, if I talk about the companies
related to the financial sector,
one from the BSF space, one from the insurance sector  There has been a lot of growth in the MC
space and the credit card business,
but if you continue to do
business in a particular competition, the
margins are geared up, and
even after increasing the business so much, which stocks are they, okay, they are
trading at the losses of 4 years ago, you can look at SBI Card,
I have talked about the insurance company,
look at the MC company, the story is also that even after so much growth,
we as shareholders have not made any money, many
stock reports on such lengths
came here, after the quarter four
results, decent results were given,
we have not discussed it in today's video
because even though it has been a long time, a
big collection has been seen in the stock from there too,
Jefferies had given a target of 1560,
GP Morgan had given a target of 1160,
Security 1245, Morgan Stanley
1400, Motilal Oswal had a target of 1400, which
means
then the highest bullish target is 15,
two friends, there is a
challenge here regarding competition in the coming time
because the premium is according to this  It will not be able to rise
because of competition, claims are coming
and expenses are increasing for these companies, so that is
one reason. In every stock
market, it is said that the stock becomes
good or bad based on its price.
ICC Lombard used to be expensive for ₹141500 earlier, from
there it seemed that there is
no upside potential, right now the stock
is quite attractive, it seems to be
around ₹5000, its 52 week low, if it
breaks that and reaches around ₹10000, then
that level
seems more attractive to me as per the stock, the
company is good, it has a big market share of around 14%,
it is the largest general insurance company in the general private sector,
so the experience that
it has had in the market for so long,
its
legacy, its benefits will keep on accruing, there are
big investments of its policies and
non-polar friends also worth ₹3000 crore,
however at that time they have released losses on their equity
portion
If we set both of them off, it is around 1.2 billion, so it is
quite big.
They had told in this quarterly, but still, if
I factor that in, then I can factor that
into today's price.
A big run has been seen in the market for the
last 1.5 months, continuously for
a month and the
market is holding on here, you are holding on,
however, as news has come in today
and SGX Nifty is indicating that tomorrow
or the day after tomorrow you may
see a new high in Nifty, but still,
in the short to medium term, I think there should be a
consolidation collection in the market, in
such a situation, you can keep such stocks on your radar.
Here, there are signs of a bottom out.
In the stock also, in MC Company, SBI
Card has shown a lot of monsters from the bottom stocks
because the recent
competitive factors, where growth is quite
expected, are
indicating a bottom out. Quality
wise, this company is very good and even Jio
Entry in the short term may be a
little negative for them, if
zero comes here, but this is
not a business which you can buy at a discount
because here the climate is a big
factor and it will remain so, this is
not such a business, competition will definitely increase but the
chances of starting such a price here are almost nil,
friends father,
you can tell me your opinion about this video in the comment section, if you
liked the video, please like it and share it with thanks.